export const Questions = [
    {
        quesNum: "1",
        prompt: "Which type of communication establishes and builds lasting relationships between people?",
        A: "One way",
        B: "Two way",
        C: "Three way",
        D: "None of these",
        ans: "B"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "2",
        prompt: "Which among these is the principle of Effective communication?",
        A: "Clarity of objective",
        B: "Selection of media",
        C: "Feedback",
        D: "All of these",
        ans: "D"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "3",
        prompt: "Communication is the task of imparting _________.",
        A: "Training",
        B: "Information",
        C: "Knowledge",
        D: "Message",
        ans: "B"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "4",
        prompt: "Which one among these is not the part of 7 C's of communication?",
        A: "Courtesy",
        B: "Clarity",
        C: "Competency",
        D: "Concrete",
        ans: "C"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "5",
        prompt: "Technical writing demands ______ use of language.",
        A: "Figurative",
        B: "Poetic",
        C: "Factual",
        D: "Dramatic",
        ans: "C"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "6",
        prompt: "Which one is avoided in technical writing?",
        A: "Fillers",
        B: "Grammar",
        C: "Punctuation",
        D: "Facts",
        ans: "A"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "7",
        prompt: "Which one among these is(are) basic requirement(s) of paragraph construction?",
        A: "Coherence",
        B: "Unity",
        C: "Emphasis",
        D: "All of these",
        ans: "D"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "8",
        prompt: "What is the meaning of the term 'Brevity'.",
        A: "Concise",
        B: "Clear",
        C: "Knowledge",
        D: "Extensive",
        ans: "A"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "9",
        prompt: "Which one of these is not a characteristic feature of language?",
        A: "Artificial",
        B: "Restricted",
        C: "Concrete",
        D: "Abstract",
        ans: "C"
    },
    {
        quesNum: "10",
        prompt: "Which is the main barrier to listening?",
        A: "Physical barrier",
        B: "Linguistic barrier",
        C: "Cultural barrier",
        D: "Physiological barrier",
        ans: "A"
    },
]